jetphotos.com 2016-06-27

# JetPhotos.Net » Privacy Policy

**Privacy policy:**  
Copyright © 2000-2015 [_JetPhotos.Net_](http://www.jetphotos.net/). All Rights Reserved. [Updated 09-25-2015]

Our users' privacy is a top priority at JetPhotos.Net. Thus, we have developed this privacy statement, which outlines in detail the privacy policies of our site.

**Cookies**   
Like most web sites, we use small bits of data called cookies stored on users' computers. Cookies are parcels of text sent by a server to a web browser and then sent back unchanged by the client each time it accesses that server. Cookies are saved on your computer and do not harm or damage your system in any way. Furthermore they make your navigation easier as they save your settings. For example, a cookie is used to remember users login credentials when they login to the website. You are able to view and control cookies through your web browser. 

JetPhotos and its partners use cookies to deliver targeted advertisements on an anonymous basis- we do not pass on any personal data to 3rd parties. Information gathered by cookies may be shared with our advertising partners to help measure the effectiveness of an advertising campaign. 

By using JetPhotos you are giving consent to cookies being used. 

**Solicitation of e-mail addresses**  
It is required that users who wish to include their photos in our database register for a free member account. At the time of registration, the user will be prompted for, among other things, his/her email address. This information will be used solely to provide an avenue for database visitors to contact the user. The email address will not be publicly displayed at any time, and all correspondence will be sent through a secure web-form, protecting the user. All user email addresses remain confidential.

**Automated collection of information**   
For security purposes, IP addresses of our users are automatically recorded. In addition, when a user posts a message in the chat forums, the IP address of the posting computer is recorded. 

The collection of this information allows JetPhotos.Net to pinpoint the origin of malicious activity. User IP addresses will never be distributed publicly, and are available only to JetPhotos.Net personnel.

We store all user information in secure databases protected via a variety of access controls. This data is accessed only for the purposes specified in this privacy policy.
